♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Ibyang] Will Mama be killed?
[director] Is this your child?
- Why are you bringing her to the shoot?
- Mama!
[director] Look what happened!
Are you leaving?
[Karla] Just follow our car, okay?
[in English] Target number 1,
Kevin Martinez.
[in English] Target number 2, Boyet.
[Emerson] That's the courier.
Make sure you don't get caught.
And most importantly, no one dies.
[Emerson] We have another companion
that Atoy shouldn't know about.
- [Gavin, in English] Hi, guys.
- Gavin?!
[Karla] What are you doing here?
Brother caught me, so…
he allowed me to join.
- [Karla] What will your role be?
- [Ame] Mm-hmm.
He'll be the lookout
outside the function room.
[Emerson, in English] One, two, three…
- [all, in English] Let's go!
- [in English] Go!
[host, in English]
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
[in English] Welcome
to Palladium Auction House.
PREVIOUSLY
Maybe Mama doesn't want me
to be her child anymore.
I'm sure she loves you.
[Cathy on phone, in English]
Babe, where are you?
Maybe we can still meet?
I just accompanied Mommy to an event.
Sorry, I already have plans.
I went with Jason to Batangas.
[in English] I think
he's going to visit someone.
[in English] Uh, let's just talk tomorrow?
[in English] Yes, yes.
[in English] My name
is Jose Bernardo Carandang!
[in English] Is this, uh,
0900-020001-00?
[in English] Correct!
[in English] She gave you
a different number.
[in English] Yes, she did.
[in English] To what
do I owe this pleasure?
[in English] Do you have a tracker?
[in English] Is there something
or someone you need to find?
[security officer, in English]
This man, Mr. Regalia.
[in English] He broke into our embassy
and stole from us.
[clears throat]
[in English] Is there
something wrong, Mr. Regalia?
[in English] Do you happen
to know this person, Mr. Regalia?
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Are you accusing me
of being connected to this man?
[in English] No, no, no, Mr. Regalia.
[in English] Forgive us.
[in English] But we still need
the contact number of the tracker.
[in English] Please.
[in English] Actually,
I tried calling him recently,
but, uh, the number that I have
is no longer active.
[in English] Maybe he changed his number.
[in English] I have
no other way to contact him.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] I'm very sorry, gentlemen,
but I couldn't help you.
[in English] Thank you
for your time, Mr. Regalia.
[tense music playing]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[clacking]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[music fades]
[door lock clicks, door hinge squeaks]
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[in English] Ms. Audrey.
[door hinge squeaks]
[in English] Nice to see you again.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Are you hiding from me?
[sighs]
[in English] Of course not.
[in English] Why would I do that?
[in English] Well, you gave me
the wrong number the other day.
[in English] What is the matter?
[in English] You don't like me?
[in English] Look.
[in English] I think
you got the wrong idea.
[in English] Um, and I'm sorry
about the wrong number.
[in English] But I just
don't like you like that.
[in English] Now, if you'll excuse me.
[tense music playing]
[in English] What is the matter?
[in English] You have someone else?
[in English] You have a lover?
[in English] Maybe a boyfriend
that you can't stop thinking about.
[in English] Is he better than me?
[in English] Yes!
[in English] A thousand times better.
[in English] Maybe he's good in bed, no?
[in English] You give me a try
to make you feel real good.
You're vulgar!
Audrey?
[in English] Dad!
[tense music playing]
[in English] What's going on?
[in English] I was just leaving.
[Cathy, in English] Thank you.
[sighs]
[in English] Child,
will you stop frowning?
You might bring me bad luck.
I want something.
[in English] I really want to bid for it.
- [in English] Sorry, Mommy.
- [mom sighs]
[suspicious music playing]
I thought you'd see Gavin?
Not anymore.
[in English] He has other plans.
He went out of town with his friend.
In the past, one call from me
and he'd come.
[in English] But now it's like
he's growing distant.
[in English] You think
there's someone else?
[in English] Maybe, um, another girl?
[in English] No.
Gavin isn't like that.
He wouldn't cheat on me.
[in English] You never know with men.
Dear, don't be complacent.
[in English] Well…
there is this… this one girl.
[in English] You see.
But she's just his best friend.
Gavin wouldn't like her.
[in English] She's just one of the boys.
[music fades]
- Cathy?
- [in English] Congratulations.
[suspicious music playing]
Usually, those best friends
are opportunists, my child.
[in English] So, you better be careful.
[in English] Okay?
[in English] Is that…
Karla?
Thread 2, this is Thread 1.
Why did you leave?
Watch over Needle.
I'm compromised, Thread 1.
Someone here recognized me,
and I had to avoid them.
Don't leave me. Karla, please.
Ah, Thread 3?
Is the outfit for Thread 4 ready?
Thread 3?
Thread 3, can you hear me?
[tense music playing]
What's happening?
These threads are getting tangled.
We're going to fail.
Oh, sis, here. Here it is, hmm.
I'm nervous.
What is this?
- [in English] Two… Two hundred thousand?
- Huh?
Just for a camera lens?!
This costs 200,000?!
This is crazy! What is this?!
How will we manage?
Well, at least
they didn't charge you for the lights
and the expensive clothes
that belongs to the producer.
Still!
It's unfair!
I didn't do this, right?
Is this my fault? Did I cause this?
Come on, let it go.
At least you have money to pay for it.
Anyway, next month,
you'll have money again, right?
- So, it's fine.
- Still!
What? The money
just passed through my hands?
There's nothing left?
All gone? Zero! What?
[sneaky music playing]
Unbelievable.
[phone ringing]
Oh. Hey, Papa Atoy!
- Why is he calling?
- Oh! Hey.
Your face, shift your emotion.
You can't sound angry.
[in English] Shift.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Hi! Yes, you called?
Olga, I spoke to the child.
She said she did something wrong to you.
Yes.
It seems she inherited my mischievousness.
[Atoy on phone] Why didn't you
tell her about your job?
And you left her alone at home.
Uh…
She said she's willing to wait at home.
[smirks] Even so.
See, because of the kid's concern for you,
she even brought you food.
What if something bad happened to her?
Then, sorry!
I didn't mean it.
I won't do it again. I'm sorry.
[Atoy on phone] Olga.
Ibyang has been looking
and praying for you for a long time.
She's not looking for a luxurious life.
As long as she's with you,
she's already happy with that.
Okay, thank you.
[in English] Bye-bye.
[gentle music playing]
Atoy is unbelievable.
Your setup is extraordinary.
- [in English] Co-parenting?
- Hey!
Could he be the father?
That Ibyang.
She better watch out
when we get home later.
She probably thinks
she can have a mediator.
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] This very special pair
of ruby-encrusted boots
was worn by Lady Gigi,
from her last concert in Manila.
[in English] Exciting!
[in English] The bid starts
at 1,000,000 pesos.
[in English] One point one million!
[host, in English] 1.1 million! From
the gentleman at the back! Number 51!
[in English] One point two million!
[host, in English] One point two million
from the lady! Number 22!
[in English] One point five million.
[in English] One point five million
from the gentleman. Number 13!
[in English] One point six million!
[host, in English] One point six million
from the gentleman. Number 66!
[suspicious music playing]
[Emerson] Sir, are you the one
investigating?
Is there any update on the theft case?
None yet.
And the longer it takes, the smaller
the chance of recovering the money.
This policeman seems to have
a lot of money.
Thread 2, do you have
a sighting of Scissors?
Negative. No Scissors yet.
[in English] One point seven million.
[in English] One point seven
from the lady! Number 34!
- Son of a thread! Cathy!
- [smirks]
[in English] OMG!
[in English] I knew it was you.
I thought I was just imagining things.
[in English] What are you doing here?
Just hustling.
Hmm.
[in English] I'm here with my mom.
[in English] She likes to bid on rare art.
Ah, okay. I'll go back to my work now.
[in English] Wait!
[in English] I wanted
to ask you something.
Are you still talking to Gavin?
Huh?
[mellow music playing]
Um, no. He's busy with you.
[in English] Uh, not really.
He chose to hang out with Jason
instead of me.
[in English] I have a feeling. Is he
- cheating on me?
- No.
Gavin wouldn't do that to you.
He's not that kind of person, Cathy.
[host, in English]
One point eight million pesos
from the gentleman. Number 62!
[in English] One point nine million.
[host, in English] One point nine million
from the gentleman. Number 66!
[in English] Two million.
[in English] Two million pesos
from the gentleman. Number 13!
[in English] Do I hear 2.1 million?
[rousing music playing]
[host, in English] For two million pesos…
[in English] Going once, going twice!
[in English] 2,100,001 pesos.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[in English] From the lady. Number 75!
[in English] Two million
and 200,000 pesos.
[in English] Two point three million!
[in English] Two point four million.
[in English] 2,450,000 pesos!
[in English] Exciting! [gasps]
What are you doing?
We don't have money to pay
if you win this.
[in English] Oh, sorry.
I got carried away
because it's fun to pretend
we have lots of money.
You really are something.
[in English] Two point five million.
[in English] Two point five million!
[in English] Do I hear any millions?
He can have it. It wouldn't fit me anyway.
Mm-hmm.
[laughing]
[host, in English] Ladies and gentlemen,
the ruby-encrusted boots
for 2.5 million
from the gentleman.
- [in English] Sold!
- [in English] Thank you.
[applauding]
[Kevin] Thank you.
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[in English] Have a seat.
[in English] Thank you, Dad.
Are you sure that man didn't hurt you?
[in English] I'm fine.
But, Dad, why are you meeting with Samir?
They're asking me to connect them…
to a tracker I know.
[in English] You mean Atoy?
[in English] Yes.
[pensive music playing]
[Dmitri] And when they showed me the photo
of the man they're looking for,
it was Atoy.
They think he's the one
who broke into the embassy.
[rousing music playing]
[in English] What's that?
[grunts]
[gasps]
- Why did you do that?!
- Shh!
[sighs] Really?
Um, what did you tell them, Dad?
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Nothing.
[Dmitri] I said…
I can't contact the tracker anymore.
I don't know
if I'll ever talk to Atoy again
after everything that happened
between him and Red.
But I won't expose Atoy.
He's still Janine's father.
[music fades]
[sentimental music playing]
[in English] Thank you, Dad.
Thank you for protecting Atoy,
for Janine's sake.
[in English] But promise me, child.
You'll stay away from Atoy.
That's what I've been doing, Dad.
That's why Janine and I are leaving.
We're just waiting for her US visa,
and then we're gone.
[in English] I know
it's not going to be easy,
but you're doing the right thing.
[in English] Child, can you just imagine
the danger he can bring to you and Janine?
If you and Atoy get back together?
[in English] He's involved in a theft,
at an embassy, of all places.
And we don't even know
what other underground connections he has.
[in English] It is best
you stay away from him.
[in English] Okay?
Here, sir.
[in English] Thank you.
[phone blips]
I'M HERE NOW
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
Needle on the move.
He received a text message
from someone with the letter B.
Looks like he's about to meet Scissors.
Okay, I'll follow him.
Sir, can I ask for some juice?
- Uh, oh…
- Me too.
Ah…
Uh… Eh, uh…
Okay! Okay, sure, sure.
Uh…
Thread 1 is compromised.
[in English] Help.
This is Thread 3.
I'll take care of Needle.
[music fades]
[pensive music playing]
Madame!
Are you also a fan of Lady Gigi?
You know, I really love those boots.
[clicks tongue]
Yes, that's why I bid on it.
But then I thought,
I wouldn't even wear them.
My boyfriend stopped me.
He said our budget
was only up to two million.
But I know he has more money.
He's so stingy, so annoying.
Hey, two million is already a lot
for a pair of boots.
Your boyfriend must be rich. Businessman?
No! Police.
There, Papa Kiko.
[suspicious music playing]
[music fades]
Who are you? Why are you following me?
[tense music playing]
Why would I follow you?
[scoffs]
I'm just going to smoke.
Where's your cigarette then?
[music fades]
Who are you?
[grunting and groaning]
- [upbeat rock music playing]
- [grunts]
[in English] I box.
- Ah, I box, huh.
- Yes.
So, I can defend myself.
[grunting and groaning]
[grunting]
I used to be a member of a syndicate, huh.
- So don't mess with me. Hmph!
- [grunts]
Ah, stop it, stop it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- [groans]
- I know you!
You're the mastermind
of the five million-peso theft!
- Huh?
- And now,
you're meeting Boyet here.
Where is he, huh?!
I don't know Boyet!
[in English] But anyway,
it's nice talking to you.
[in English] Mm-hmm. Nice meeting you.
- [in English] Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
[sneaky music playing]
Psst, hmm.
You know, you're unbelievable.
You're chatting away
while we're struggling
over there watching Needle.
And you, you're just chatting here.
Hmm? It's not my fault
that I'm the one who looks like
a rich lady among the four of us.
[scoffs] Wow!
So full of yourself!
Unbelievable.
Anyway, just be careful
with what you're saying
to Meneses's child, okay?
You might say something wrong.
Meneses?
Do you know Cherry's boyfriend?
- Boyfriend?
- Yes.
Papa Kiko.
Cherry isn't his child,
she's his girlfriend.
Kiko?
His real name is Francisco Meneses.
Kiko is just his nickname.
You're really slow.
Hmm, that policeman has a lot of money.
[phone ringing]
[suspicious music playing]
[groans]
- Wait a second.
- [chuckles]
- Yes. Yeah.
- Hello, boss!
[Boyet] Yes.
Your suitcase is here.
[music fades]
[muffled chattering in the distance]
- [thumps]
- [groans]
Sorry, sorry.
Watch where you're going.
Be thankful I'm in a hurry.
Thank you.
Thread 1, can you hear me?
Spotted Scissors, carrying the button.
What? What?
Boyet is here, carrying the suitcase.
[Karla on the device] You and your codes,
you're just confusing yourself.
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Boss.
Mmm.
Ame, we were wrong.
Hmm?
Boss KM is Kiko Meneses,
not Kevin Martinez.
We've been following the wrong Needle.
Who is Boyet?!
What do you mean you don't know?!
Don't lie!
- Huh!
- I'm not lying.
- I don't know Boyet!
- Hey! Hey!
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
What's your problem? What's your problem?
Let go of my boyfriend!
What?!
He's the one I'm meeting here!
His name isn't Boyet, it's Mikey!
I'm giving him the boots
I won at the auction!
- OMG! Really?
- [in English] Yes. Surprise, honey!
Eh, so who's the one…
Who were you messaging… the letter B?
[smirks]
B, my Baby!
[Kevin] Wait.
How do you know his name in my cellphone?
- Huh?
- [Emerson on the device] Thread 3?
Thread 3, can you hear me?
[in English] Abort. Thread 3, abort!
You're following the wrong Needle.
Ame and I know who the real Needle is.
It's Kiko Meneses.
He's the policeman investigating the case.
[in English] Sorry, sorry.
Needle 2 and Scissors on the move,
with the Button.
[in English] Thread 2 in pursuit.
So, what? Should we follow too?
Let's go.
Oh, oh. Where are you going?
You gave the wrong drink.
Raspberry iced tea, not lemon.
[Emerson] Oh, is that so?
Uh, all right, sir.
I'll replace it…
- I'll go ahead, okay.
- Ah, um…
Ah-- Ah, wait a second.
Wait a second.
[rousing music playing]
Mama!
[objects clattering and clanging]
[gasping]
[squeals]
[objects clattering]
Cut! You're disturbing my set!
Who are you?!
You broke the equipment!
- She's my mom.
- [director] Huh?
This is your child?
Why are you bringing her to the shoot?
Look what happened!
I'll take care of it!
[squeals] You're driving me crazy!
[director] And your dream, huh?
Your dream of becoming famous?
Forget it.
[rousing music playing]
[somber music playing]
Sorry. [sobs]
I'm really sorry, Ma! [sobs]
You're the one at fault,
and yet you snitched on me
to your pretend-father?
But Tatoy said… [sobs]
to tell the truth.
And it seemed they were going
to kill you for real. [sobs]
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
I don't want to lose my mother again.
What's wrong with you?! That's not true!
Huh? That was just acting!
We were taping…
My God.
Haven't you seen a shoot before?
We were just pretending.
We're just acting!
When you said…
you missed me,
was that acting too?
What?
[sobbing]
Because when I came home,
it felt like you weren't ready for me.
And you're always angry at me.
- [music fades]
- [sobs]
Am I really your child?
[epic music playing]
- [electronic blipping]
- [tense music playing]
[Karla] Thread 1, Scissors
carrying the Button.
They're checking in.
Mini Thread.
‪UP NEXT
[in English] I have a bright idea.
What's the plan for the child?
Don't worry about that.
Just do what we agreed on.
That's your only job. Okay?
We'll get a room,
and that's where we'll count the money.
- Ah.
- If there's anything missing.
[Boyet] It's complete.
Hmph! I'm not going with you!
Wait. You're causing trouble!
[grunts]
[Boyet] Let go of me!
- Audrey?
- [Audrey] Samir and the others have
an AI-generated photo of your face.
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix this ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias